"Mr. Speaker,
will the 30s go down as the decade...
"which witnessed the destruction...
"and downfall of the British empire?"
"That witnessed
the wanton self-destruction...
"of the British empire?"
"If India were granted...
"self-government...
"it would mark the downfall
of the British empire."
"It would mark and consummate...
"the downfall of the British empire."
Mr. Inches, you're wanted!
On my way.
* Good morning.
* Good morning, madam.
Have to do something
about Miss Sarah's gramophone.
I don't want to start the day
with a family altercation.
* No, madam.
* Hello, Mommy.
Good morning, darling.
Inches, kindly tell my daughter
to turn off that bloody gramophone.
Trashy music all over the house.
There you go, sir.
She knows I can't stand it.
Why does she do it?
Leave it to me, sir, will you?
Have you been drinking?
This time of the morning, sir? Certainly not.
If you have,
I hope it's your damn whisdey and not mine.
What time is Mrs. P coming?
Early afternoon, sir.
* Early afternoon? Why not this morning?
* Because you told her to come after lunch.
Pure invention, I did nothing of the sort.
You said you're going
to town this morning...
so she would not be required
until after lunch.
I've changed my mind,
I need to redraft the speech.